Then when we tokenize text,
当我们对文本分词时
we often use either the frequency of the words as a feature or even better to TFIDF,
我们经常使用单词的频率作为特征 更好的方法是使用 TFIDF
Term Frequency Inverse Document
TFIDF
Frequency that represents the relative specificity over word.
表示相关单词在文本中的重要程度
Spark has built the methods to compute both of these.
Spark有计算这两者的内置方法
We can use the CountVectorizer to get the word counts.
我们可以使用 CountVectorizer 来获取单词计数
We can set how many words we would like to keep.
我们可以设置我们想保留多少个单词
Here I chose a vocabSize of 1,000,
在这里 我选择了1000的vocabSize
meaning that we'll keep the top 1,000 most common words.
表示我们将保留最常见的1000个单词
Spark stores the word counts as a sparse vector.
Spark 将单词计数存储为稀疏向量
So for example, the first record has the 0th word,
例如 第一个记录 第一个
four times the first one,
是四倍
six times the second one,
第二个是六倍
two times and so far so on.
第三个是两倍 等等
The calling vocabulary, we can see the list of words we use in the CV model.
调用词汇表 我们可以看到在 cvmodel 中使用的单词列表
Here you can see the first few in
你可以看到前几个单词
contractariser the zeros in next goes to the most common word.
在 CountVectorizer 方法里第一个是最常见的词
So in this case,
这里就是这个 p
this is p. If you remember the HTML tag for a paragraph of a space,
如果你还记得 HTML用 P 标记段落
so probably that's why the CP is open.
这可能就是P为啥这么常见的原因了
There are some other very common words,
还有其他一些很常见的词
for example, 'the', 'a', 'code.'
例如 'the' 'a' 'code'
Lots of calling questions it seems,
似乎有很多比较的问题
'is' 'and' and similar words like that.
'is' 'and' 以及其他类似的词
We can also take a look at the least common ones.
我们还可以看看最不常见的单词
Here we see less common words such as customer,
我们看到不太常见的词 如 customer
desktop, buttons and a few others.
Desktop  buttons 和其他一些单词
Then we compute the TFIDF,
接下来我们计算TFIDF
we can see that the relative frequency of the words at the beginning of the vector,
我们可以在向量的开头看到单词的相对频率
so the 0th first,
先是第0个 第一个
these are the words that are the most common in our data set has dropped.
这些是我们的数据集中最常见的单词
So, TFIDF effectively surpasses the stop words as we expected.
TFIDF 有效地把停用词做了限制
As the last step, let's turn the one tag field that contains strings into numeric values.
最后我们将包含字符串的 onetag 字段转换为数值型
The one tag field contains the most common tag,
Onetag 字段对整个数据集中问题的标签进行计算
calculated over the whole data set of the tags of a particular question.
选取最常见的那个标签
So for example, if a question was tagged with Java and load,
例如 如果一个问题有 Java 和 load 这两个标签
I can tag Java,
我们就选取 Java 作为标签
since it's more common than the tag load.
因为它比 load 更常见
In this previous example,
在前面的例子中
among the tags PHP image processing file upload,
Tag 包括 PHP、image processing、 file upload
upload mime-types, the one tag column
以及upload mime-types
became PHP since this was the most common among these five tags.
Onetag 的值是PHP 因为这是这几个标签中最常见的
We can use the string indexing method,
我们可以使用 stringIndexer方法
to do this transformation.
对数据做这个转换
Looking at this example,
看看这个例子
the tag PHP became label three.
标签 PHP 转换为标签 3
String indexer gives the 0th index and
stringIndexer 会给出第0个索引和
the most common string and then goes in ascending order.
最常见的字符串然后按升序排列
So, PHP is one of the most common tags in our data set.
所以 PHP 是数据集中最常见的标记之一
The reason why we might want to transform a string value to a numeric one is because
我们之所以把字符串值转换为数字值是因为
Spark similarly to other frameworks need numeric values both
与其他框架类似 Spark需要数值
as features and targets to compute machine-learning models.
作为计算机器学习模型的特征和目标